<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>What I thought on waneal blog</title>
    <link>https://waneal.github.io/tags/what-i-thought/</link>
    <description>Recent content in What I thought on waneal blog</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://waneal.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 23:16:10 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waneal.github.io/tags/what-i-thought/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>20210517</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210517/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 23:16:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210517/</guid>
      <description>  I watched Sicario. Landscape and color usage are incredible. Especially, the scene I remained in my heart is that soldiers walking in sunset.
  It was moist day today, I wanted to dive in the sea without clothes.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210516</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210516/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 22:07:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210516/</guid>
      <description>I often tweet by Twitter. My tweet topics contain Tech, NBA, News, and soliloquy, but they&amp;rsquo;re not related in this blog.
The idea was born, and knead words I know. Finally, when considered sentence is ready for tweet, I think why I tweet. While writing sentence, I had no doubt that this tweet must be cool, but finished writing, I noticed the sentence seems like meaningless. What I want to say is that tweet is difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210514</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210514/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 21:40:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210514/</guid>
      <description>Through this weekday, I&amp;rsquo;m exhausted. I slept 7 hours yesterday, but I felt not getting satisfied sleep when I get up today. Fatigue is still living in my body. I know the reason, it&amp;rsquo;s Golden Week Syndrome, other calls May Syndrome. I want to rest my body and brain with fluffy bed all day.
Good night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210513</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210513/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 11:59:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210513/</guid>
      <description>When we find solution which solves something big problem, it is important that we firstly define As-Is and To-Be. In my case, I sometime forget it and find concrete solution first. I understand it is my bad habit.
Today, I realized that I&amp;rsquo;m in the situation, and I wrote this blog to not forget this.
I want to let you know my KIMOCHI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210511</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210511/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 23:14:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210511/</guid>
      <description>When I stood in the position to teach someone, I felt that I should make myself correct. Telling someone with doubt or no consent, it makes me feel bad. It&amp;rsquo;s important to go outside for refresh. In coronavirus crisis, I&amp;rsquo;m working in my house, so I don&amp;rsquo;t have opportunity to get some fresh air if I have no plan to go out. Being in the house all day, I get crazy like a mob in Bloodborne.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
