<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Diary on waneal blog</title>
    <link>https://waneal.github.io/categories/diary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Diary on waneal blog</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://waneal.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 21:40:58 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waneal.github.io/categories/diary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>20210514</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210514/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 21:40:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210514/</guid>
      <description>Through this weekday, I&amp;rsquo;m exhausted. I slept 7 hours yesterday, but I felt not getting satisfied sleep when I get up today. Fatigue is still living in my body. I know the reason, it&amp;rsquo;s Golden Week Syndrome, other calls May Syndrome. I want to rest my body and brain with fluffy bed all day.
Good night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210513</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210513/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 11:59:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210513/</guid>
      <description>When we find solution which solves something big problem, it is important that we firstly define As-Is and To-Be. In my case, I sometime forget it and find concrete solution first. I understand it is my bad habit.
Today, I realized that I&amp;rsquo;m in the situation, and I wrote this blog to not forget this.
I want to let you know my KIMOCHI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210511</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210511/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 23:14:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210511/</guid>
      <description>When I stood in the position to teach someone, I felt that I should make myself correct. Telling someone with doubt or no consent, it makes me feel bad. It&amp;rsquo;s important to go outside for refresh. In coronavirus crisis, I&amp;rsquo;m working in my house, so I don&amp;rsquo;t have opportunity to get some fresh air if I have no plan to go out. Being in the house all day, I get crazy like a mob in Bloodborne.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New family member</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/new_family_member/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 23:12:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/new_family_member/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, we welcomed a new family member.
It was at 08:00 pm when he came to home with his driver. As soon as he arrived, he began walking all over the house without saying hello. I felt him rude. But I noticed that there is no trash behind the way he walked. He was the professional.
This is him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first blog post</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/my_first_blog_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 11:44:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/my_first_blog_post/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I am waneal. This is my first blog post. From now on, I will post various types of blogs.
The aim of this blog is to learn English. I usually read English texts to understand specification of some tools, but not write. Generally, living in Japan, we do not use english to let someone know something, and so I want to make a habit of using English. For the people usually using english, it is so easy to post a short English blog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
