<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>What I thought on waneal blog</title>
    <link>https://waneal.github.io/tags/what-i-thought/</link>
    <description>Recent content in What I thought on waneal blog</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://waneal.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 00:43:44 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waneal.github.io/tags/what-i-thought/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>20210605</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210605/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 00:43:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210605/</guid>
      <description>I ate a Milan-style doria cooked by my wife, she used this as a reference. It was so great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210603</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210603/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 01:07:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210603/</guid>
      <description>I ate grilled fish with salsa, that was all of today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210602</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210602/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:13:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210602/</guid>
      <description>I have one of the best movies, it&amp;rsquo;s The Equalizer. Thanks to this movie, I knew Denzel Washington, and he became my favorite actor. In this movie, one sentence shook my heart.
 Progress. Not Perfection.
 Denzel Washington is a main character. His colleague aiming to be a cop needs to lose weight, but he tried to eat chips which he hid into sandwich, and Denzel Washington told him it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210601</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210601/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 23:41:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210601/</guid>
      <description>It doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel real yet. It is very special day today, off course it doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean tacos&#39; day. Maybe, I don&amp;rsquo;t believe and feel it real until I see it by my own eyes. Wow, this is so poetical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210531</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210531/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 23:43:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210531/</guid>
      <description>I ate fried udon noodles, that is all of today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210530</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210530/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 23:15:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210530/</guid>
      <description>It is the special day in my family today. It&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;Taco Sunday&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;Taco Tuesday&amp;rdquo;? I don&amp;rsquo;t know it. We eat a more huge tacos than it sold by normal restaurant, off course we cook it by ourselves. A bowl full of mined meat, fresh lettuce, salsa source to change the taste, and shredded cheese. I had a great time, I&amp;rsquo;ll do my best this weekdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210529</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210529/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 23:49:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210529/</guid>
      <description>I watched &amp;ldquo;Attack on Titan&amp;rdquo; season 1 with my wife. Characters are attractive, and their dialogue shake our hearts. Maybe, we will watch all seasons through this weekend.
  I cooked packaged instant ramen for the first time because I always eat cup of instant ramen. In addition to cook according to description of package, I made boiled egg, cut a green onion, and attached a seaweed. It was so great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210526</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210526/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 23:32:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210526/</guid>
      <description> I ate the crazy Okonomiyaki cooked by my wife. That is all the today.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210525</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210525/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 22:18:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210525/</guid>
      <description>  It is payday today. I love it the best in the all day of 31 days. Marry me.
  Even if in a boring meeting, be paying attention. our next task will be based on it.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210524</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210524/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 22:43:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210524/</guid>
      <description>Working at night makes me high, maybe a lot of adrenaline are created by my brain. However, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t generate high productivity. Coming dawn, I reviewed progress of yesterday, I found some mistakes in minute. Shut down our laptop, and we have to go to bed as soon as possible.
  Reporting is not just for your boss, but also for yours. In summarizing the report, we can organize that we think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210523</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210523/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 23:19:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210523/</guid>
      <description>I add new function for posting this blog, it is an auto deployment by GitHub Actions. I found some convenient actions helping to update GitHub Pages, and could create deployment configuration easily. However, deployment in GitHub Pages has not been finished from now yet (Maybe, it is not related with these actions). It spent over an hour in Page Build phase. I give up to make sure of finish today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210521</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210521/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 00:06:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210521/</guid>
      <description>I was talking with my friend from college. Topics are almost about our job. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of opportunity that we talk about serious topics, so it was valuable time for me. Spending over 30 years, the timing I think deeply about my job absolutely comes. Maybe, we&amp;rsquo;re in the timing.
  I pre-ordered Biomutant. I can not wait to play it. Absolutely, my character will be in the dark side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210520</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210520/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 22:12:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210520/</guid>
      <description> For characteristic of my job, I almost have a lot of task to do, so each task tends to be delayed. I frequently say sorry because of sense of guilt. This is also my bad habit. I will say no sorry from now anytime.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210519</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210519/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 22:24:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210519/</guid>
      <description>Standing on weight scale, amazing numerical value appeared. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe it. Of course, I know what be not enough for me. I know, I know. Then now, I&amp;rsquo;m drinking a canned chu-hai. I will do my best from tomorrow.
  I miss to play basketball. Because of coronavirus, almost sports centers and gymnasium are forbidden to use. The only method to shake off my sorrow is watching NBA game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210518</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210518/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 23:33:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210518/</guid>
      <description>I watched Sicario: Day of the Soldado. To tell the truth, I had begun watching it before I watched the first one, so I couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand background of characters, and stopped watching. After I watched first one, it caught my attention. Sicario series seems to have three titles, and this second one had dramatic ending hinting the story of third one. I cannot wait next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210517</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210517/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 23:16:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210517/</guid>
      <description>  I watched Sicario. Landscape and color usage are incredible. Especially, the scene I remained in my heart is that soldiers walking in sunset.
  It was moist day today, I wanted to dive in the sea without clothes.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210516</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210516/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 22:07:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210516/</guid>
      <description>I often tweet by Twitter. My tweet topics contain Tech, NBA, News, and soliloquy, but they&amp;rsquo;re not related in this blog.
The idea was born, and knead words I know. Finally, when considered sentence is ready for tweet, I think why I tweet. While writing sentence, I had no doubt that this tweet must be cool, but finished writing, I noticed the sentence seems like meaningless. What I want to say is that tweet is difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210514</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210514/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 21:40:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210514/</guid>
      <description>Through this weekday, I&amp;rsquo;m exhausted. I slept 7 hours yesterday, but I felt not getting satisfied sleep when I get up today. Fatigue is still living in my body. I know the reason, it&amp;rsquo;s Golden Week Syndrome, other calls May Syndrome. I want to rest my body and brain with fluffy bed all day.
Good night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210513</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210513/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 11:59:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210513/</guid>
      <description>When we find solution which solves something big problem, it is important that we firstly define As-Is and To-Be. In my case, I sometime forget it and find concrete solution first. I understand it is my bad habit.
Today, I realized that I&amp;rsquo;m in the situation, and I wrote this blog to not forget this.
I want to let you know my KIMOCHI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210511</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210511/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 23:14:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210511/</guid>
      <description>When I stood in the position to teach someone, I felt that I should make myself correct. Telling someone with doubt or no consent, it makes me feel bad. It&amp;rsquo;s important to go outside for refresh. In coronavirus crisis, I&amp;rsquo;m working in my house, so I don&amp;rsquo;t have opportunity to get some fresh air if I have no plan to go out. Being in the house all day, I get crazy like a mob in Bloodborne.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
