<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>waneal blog</title>
    <link>https://waneal.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on waneal blog</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://waneal.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 23:00:43 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waneal.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Executable files information of go</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/executable_files_information_of_go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 23:00:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/executable_files_information_of_go/</guid>
      <description>go version -m can print module dependency of executable file&amp;rsquo;s code.
&amp;gt; go version -m /usr/local/bin/peco /usr/local/bin/peco: go1.14.5 path command-line-arguments mod github.com/peco/peco (devel) dep github.com/google/btree v0.0.0-20161213163243-0c3044bc8bad h1:IIXE5Gtu2VS7SL3lhB61iSliE+jpOwuYDYAH4HGxGwY= dep github.com/jessevdk/go-flags v1.1.0 h1:Geou1o2RJhW9nUu+puVL2ASZMWjfj6+uy97+byGKL98= dep github.com/lestrrat-go/pdebug v0.0.0-20180220043849-39f9a71bcabe h1:S7XSBlgc/eI2v47LkPPVa+infH3FuTS4tPJbqCtJovo= dep github.com/mattn/go-runewidth v0.0.0-20161012013512-737072b4e32b h1:idzeyUe3K4aU/SIZWMykIkJJyTD7CgDkxUQEjV07fno= dep github.com/nsf/termbox-go v0.0.0-20190817171036-93860e161317 h1:hhGN4SFXgXo61Q4Sjj/X9sBjyeSa2kdpaOzCO+8EVQw= dep github.com/pkg/errors v0.0.0-20161029093637-248dadf4e906 h1:aXc/AM323HlkOXjl3QuSO06wbXK45HrzBT+pwVOufXg= https://golang.org/pkg/cmd/go/internal/version/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210516</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210516/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 22:07:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210516/</guid>
      <description>I often tweet by Twitter. My tweet topics contain Tech, NBA, News, and soliloquy, but they&amp;rsquo;re not related in this blog.
The idea was born, and knead words I know. Finally, when considered sentence is ready for tweet, I think why I tweet. While writing sentence, I had no doubt that this tweet must be cool, but finished writing, I noticed the sentence seems like meaningless. What I want to say is that tweet is difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210514</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210514/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 21:40:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210514/</guid>
      <description>Through this weekday, I&amp;rsquo;m exhausted. I slept 7 hours yesterday, but I felt not getting satisfied sleep when I get up today. Fatigue is still living in my body. I know the reason, it&amp;rsquo;s Golden Week Syndrome, other calls May Syndrome. I want to rest my body and brain with fluffy bed all day.
Good night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210513</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210513/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 11:59:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210513/</guid>
      <description>When we find solution which solves something big problem, it is important that we firstly define As-Is and To-Be. In my case, I sometime forget it and find concrete solution first. I understand it is my bad habit.
Today, I realized that I&amp;rsquo;m in the situation, and I wrote this blog to not forget this.
I want to let you know my KIMOCHI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deregister unused instances in SSM</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/deregister_unused_instances_in_ssm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 21:29:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/deregister_unused_instances_in_ssm/</guid>
      <description>AWS Systems Manager can manage instances by Fleet Manager. It can cover not only aws instances, but also on-premiss instances by Hybrid Activations. For example, using Hybrid Activations and managing servers which are under control of auto-scaling function in on-premiss environment, some servers become ConnectionLost status in Fleet Manager when their servers are terminated by scale in action. At result, unused servers continue existing in Fleet Manager.
To resolve that problem, I regularly clean up unused instances by below lambda function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20210511</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210511/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 23:14:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/20210511/</guid>
      <description>When I stood in the position to teach someone, I felt that I should make myself correct. Telling someone with doubt or no consent, it makes me feel bad. It&amp;rsquo;s important to go outside for refresh. In coronavirus crisis, I&amp;rsquo;m working in my house, so I don&amp;rsquo;t have opportunity to get some fresh air if I have no plan to go out. Being in the house all day, I get crazy like a mob in Bloodborne.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New family member</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/new_family_member/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 23:12:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/new_family_member/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, we welcomed a new family member.
It was at 08:00 pm when he came to home with his driver. As soon as he arrived, he began walking all over the house without saying hello. I felt him rude. But I noticed that there is no trash behind the way he walked. He was the professional.
This is him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first blog post</title>
      <link>https://waneal.github.io/posts/my_first_blog_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 11:44:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waneal.github.io/posts/my_first_blog_post/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I am waneal. This is my first blog post. From now on, I will post various types of blogs.
The aim of this blog is to learn English. I usually read English texts to understand specification of some tools, but not write. Generally, living in Japan, we do not use english to let someone know something, and so I want to make a habit of using English. For the people usually using english, it is so easy to post a short English blog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
